pointblankmusicschool.com 2017-02-09

# Point Blank Online | Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy sets out how we will treat the personal information which you provide to us while using the websites located at www.pointblanklondon.com (“Sites”) and/or the services provided from the Sites (“Services”). You are deemed to accept the terms of this Privacy Policy on your first use of either Site. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time and such changes shall be effective from the date and time the revised Privacy Policy is posted on the Sites. The Sites, together with all content are owned or controlled by Point Blank Limited, with its registered office at 23-28 Penn St, London N1 5DL.

To provide the Sites and the Services, it is necessary for us to hold and process certain personal information. We take reasonable care in keeping this information secure and preventing any unauthorised access or unlawful use of it. All personal information is processed by us in accordance with applicable data protection legislation.

From time to time, we may collect or ask you to provide some or all of the following: name, address, date of birth, gender, email addresses and/or mobile phone numbers, financial information, IP addresses, web-browser details, operating system details, and/or your activities on the Sites. This information will be stored together with any additional information you may provide to us from time to time, and will be used to provide you with the Services and any other services associated with them. We may also use your personal information to analyse use of the Sites and/or to keep you up-to-date with other products and services provided by Point Blank or from our trusted partners which we think may be of interest to you.

We will only keep your personal information for as long as is necessary. We may, from time to time, expand or reduce our business and this may involve the sale of certain divisions or the transfer of control of certain divisions to other parties. Data provided by Users will, where relevant, be transferred and the new owner or new controlling party will, under the terms of this Privacy Policy, be permitted to use such data for the purposes for which it was supplied by you.

We may use 'cookies' while you access the Sites to avoid the need to re-enter details on different occasions. This information is used to produce statistical reports on Sites activity and allows us to tailor the Sites to suit your interests. Examples include:

  * enabling our service to recognise your device so that you don't have to give the same information several times during one task;
  * recognising that you may already have given a username and password so that you don't need to do it for every web page requested; and/or,
  * measuring how many people are using services, to make the services easier to use and to ensure sufficient capacity for quick delivery to your web browser.

A “cookie” is a small amount of data sent from the server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Most web browsers are automatically set up to accept cookies, but you can set your browser to refuse cookies or ask your browser to show you where a cookie has been set up. Please note that certain features of the Sites are only activated by the presence of a cookie and if you choose to refuse cookies these features may not be available to you. All modern browsers allow you to change your cookie settings. These settings will typically be found in the 'options' or 'preferences' menu of your browser. In order to understand these settings, the following links may be helpful (otherwise you should use the 'Help' option in your browser for more details):

  * Cookie settings in Internet Explorer
  * Cookie settings in Firefox
  * Cookie settings in Chrome
  * Cookie settings in Safari

Please note that we do not recommend turning cookies off when visiting pointblanklondon.com as this will prevent you from using many of the services on the Sites. For further information about cookies and how to control their use, please visit the following third party educational resources: [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) and [www.youronlinechoices.eu](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/).

If you do not want us to retain or use your personal information in any way, please withdraw your consent (i.e. “opt out”), by contacting us at info@pointblanklondon.com.

If you have any queries about this Privacy Policy or wish to resume receiving information which you may have previously opted-out of receiving, please contact us at please contact us at info@pointblanklondon.com.
